<uni>
<studies>
	<course>
		<title>E-Business Systems</title>
		<code>INTE2047</code>
		<lectureday>Tuesday</lectureday>
		<labday>Tuesday</labday>
		<semester>1</semester>
		<year>2013</year>
		<description>This course aims to provide an understanding of e-business and its associated technologies. 
    The basics of online commerce will be introduced along with the elements that are particular to an electronic marketplace. 
    The course covers both client-side and server-side issues as well as the associated tools and languages such as HTML, JavaScript and PHP.  
    Learning activities concentrate on the use of these tools for the purposes of finding viable e-commerce solutions. </description>
		<graphic>images/ecommerce.jpg</graphic>
	</course>
    <course>
        <title>Accounting in Organizations and Society</title>
        <code>ACCT1046</code>
        <lectureday>Tuesday</lectureday>
        <labday>Tuesday</labday>
        <semester>1</semester>
        <year>2013</year>
		<description>Accounting in Organisations and Society introduces you to the role of accounting information in business and also in society more broadly. 
    In this course you will learn the basic principles underlying the production of financial information and its use in decision-making by various user groups including managers, 
    shareholders, lenders, investment analysts, etc. 
    The course depicts accounting as the language of business communication to explain its relevance to students of all business disciplines. 
    Accounting in Organisations and Society is a compulsory core unit in the Bachelor of Business suite of degrees, and is also a pre-requisite for more advanced courses in accounting.</description>
		<graphic>images/accounting.jpg</graphic>
    </course>
    <course>
        <title>Commercial Law</title>
        <code>LAW2442</code>
        <lectureday>Wednesday</lectureday>
        <labday>Wednesday</labday>
        <semester>1</semester>
        <year>2013</year>
		<description>Successful completion of Commercial Law means that you should be able to: Analyse legal problems with an appreciation of the multiple issues impacting those problems. 
    In addition, the course provides an opportunity for you to develop generic capabilities. These include the ability to: 
    Solve problems and construct arguments,Tolerate ambiguity, Identify, understand, distinguish, interpret  and apply basic legal concepts.</description>
		<graphic>images/law.jpg</graphic>
    </course>
</studies>
</uni>